

Miguel Angel Oldemburg

Computer & IT

66

I'm a system engineer living in beautiful island in The Caribbean Sea called Margarita. Passionate about my work, motivated and hard working person. I'm a native Spanish speaker, fluent in English and currently learning French.

Accomplished software developer experienced in designing and developing complex web applications and mobile hybrid apps (Full Stack). I have a comprehensive knowledge of programming languages such as PHP (laravel | zend) and JavaScript.

Contact





+58 414 8098304

Education

Universidad de Margarita (UNIMAR) Bachelor of Engineering

Academia Prepárate PHP And MySQL Programming Complementary studies

Peter's Language Institute Advanced English Course

Basic, intermediate and advanced English Course

El Valle del Espiritu Santo, Nueva Esparta Graduated June 2014

> Porlamar, Nueva Esparta Graduated June 2014

> Porlamar, Nueva Esparta Graduated July 2010

Employment History

Vendorcenter (Argentinean company) Web Developer

Buenos Aires, Buenos Aires February 2018 - Present

Develop and test **vendorcenter.net** platform, a vendors management system (Front - Backend).

Administradora SCH

Porlamar, Nueva Esparta

Design and develop all the software projects for the company (along with another developer) most of them web-based sites (back and frontend). Write, update, and maintain all the software to handle specific jobs. Tools used: PHP, MySQL, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap.

Peter's Language Institute

Porlamar, Nueva Esparta August 2010 - July 2017

English teacher in charge of preparing classes, teaching students, evaluating and grading students' class work and homework at basic and intermediate levels. Encouraged a positive learning

Digilink c.a. (call center)

Clerk (operator)

Porlamar, Nueva Esparta November 2014 - April 2016

Professional Skills

Design HTML5 CSS3 PHP Bootstrap WordPress **Javascript**

Languages

Spanish **Native** English Fluent French **Beginner**

Publications